YASIN Z.

Istanbul, Istanbul, Turkey



zehir.yasin@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/yasin-z-848765b5

Summary

Experienced Data Analyst with a demonstrated in the information technology and defense industry.

Skills: √# Python (pandas, sklearn, numpy, seaborn, matplotlib, scipy) √# SQL **√**# HTML √# CSS ✓# JavaScript ✓# Django √# Big Data tools (Spark) ✓# Statistics ✓# Exploratory Data Analysis ✓# Data Visualization with python **√**# d3.js √# Software Testing **√**# Linux √# AWS

✓# Docker

✓# Ansible

✓# Jenkins

✓#Docker Swarm

✓# Kubernetes

Values:

- √# Make something better every day
- √# Own your mistakes so you can learn from them
- √# Details are everything
- ✓# Be truthful

Experience

Web Developer | Data Analyst

Conscience VC

Jan 2020 - Present (11 months +)

Data Analyst & Operations Research Analyst

Turkish Navy

Sep 2008 - Dec 2019 (11 years 4 months)

Operational and strategic planning, managing and leading personnel and process as an Operations Officer. Dealing with manipulating & wrangling data using Excel, Access and SQL. Through data analysis and optimization techniques, helping decision makers overcome complicated problems. Preparing and presenting daily, weekly and monthly and on-demand reports.

Education

T.N.W. College

Master's degree, International Relations and Affairs 2015 - 2016

T.N. Academy

Bachelor of Science - BS, Electrics/Electronics Engineering 2004 - 2008

Licenses & Certifications

- Bronze Life Guard AccessorieZ Online Store
- Diver CMAS World Underwater Federation
- Human Resource Management İstanbul İşletme Enstitüsü 280790060121
- **G SEO** Google
- Human Resources Strategy Udemy
- HR Oxford Home Study College
- PMI member Project Management Institute
- Certificate of Competence for Operators of Pleasure Craft Undersecretariat for Maritime Affairs
- Amateur Seaman's Certificate Undersecretariat of Maritime Affairs
- SQL SoloLearn
- 🌎 HTML SoloLearn

- Project Management (Hard) TestDome
- Accounting & Finance TestDome
- Administrative Assistant TestDome
- Business Administration İstanbul İşletme Enstitüsü 280790120011
- SQL Analytics with Apache Drill MapR Technologies 9cik39acp58j
- **Big Data** MapR Technologies 37uqqaj2nqv7
- Apache Spark MapR Technologies ov4wbxxmhv6o
- Python 3 Tutorial Course SoloLearn 1073-14960068
- Python for Data Science Cognitive Class
- Data Analysis with Python Cognitive Class
- Statistics & Python Udemy UC-FJVUQHQF/
- **Data Visualization with Python** Udemy UC-PSFDHQEG
- (A) Responsive Web Design Certification freeCodeCamp fcced1035bf-fbe5-4d34-ac4b-7f8e1dc4f783
- Artificial Intelligence (AI) Coursera
 DDC5UZ69XQNY
- What is the Data Science? Coursera
 3KXM8D6TCSPX

- Programming for Everybody (Getting Started with Python) Coursera EN5PCU2ZJMEX
 HTML, CSS, and Javascript for Web Developers Coursera KGS9D4GPVZZK
- JavaScript Tutorial SoloLearn 1024-14960068
- Mentor for Impact -Start Mentoring Udemy UC-FU24YQKC
- Programming Foundations with JavaScript, HTML and CSS Coursera d720d7490e91d75f3ef4f6e09c738932
- Interactivity with JavaScript Coursera 4882655e6352e55f48c8828adb42a193
- Data Analysis with Python Coursera
 SJ7TKDS443P4
- Structured Query Language (SQL). Coursera 2H6CXZRCPWBL
- AWS Fundamentals: Going Cloud-Native Coursera 2J2HF5THZS88
- Technical Support Coursera
 W445BPXGGM3F
- Linux for Developers Coursera
 JETKCMVEXSB7
- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp fcced1035bf-fbe5-4d34-ac4b-7f8e1dc4f783
- Version Control with Git Coursera
 G7YD4SEZ5GVR
- Google IT Support Specialization Coursera

FGUTN8NY99E7

Continuous Delivery & DevOps - Coursera RB5NWZ5Z5SD2

Docker - KodeKloud 296044

Agile with Atlassian Jira - Coursera
N3M24LVBH5BM

Information Visualization: Programming with D3.js - Coursera 78YB53C5A4A5

Ansible - KodeKloud cert_7gry1d2k

Kubernetes - KodeKloud cert_x48c8339

Skills

Teamwork • Communication • Amazon Web Services (AWS) • DevOps • Software Development • Moodle • Project Management • Mentoring • Leadership • Training